[Music]
Hello guys, welcome to Engineers
Lab.  The quarter 2 results of the well-known insurance company ICICI
LBD are out.
So let's see how the
company's quarter 2 results have been.
Talking about the company's data, in this quarter the
company has presented all the data in lakhs.
So whatever we are going to talk about, we will do it
only after converting it into crores.
If we talk about the total income of the company,
which was Rs 6582 crore in this quarter,
which was Rs 683 crore in the last quarter
and Rs 5850 crore in the previous quarter.
That means the company's income is seen
increasing from Rs 5850 crore to Rs 6582
crore on year on
year basis, which is seen growing at around 12%.
Talking about the
total expenses, which were Rs 5830 crore in this quarter,
which were Rs
5429 crore in the last quarter and Rs
5186 crore in the previous quarter.  That means the company's
expenses have increased from Rs 5186 crore to Rs 5830 crore.  The
main reason for this is the company
's net commission which seems to be increasing from Rs 844 crore to Rs
1012 crore.
If we talk about the company's profit after
taxes, PAT has been Rs 819 crore
in this quarter, which was Rs
747 crore in the last quarter and Rs
693 crore in the last same quarter.  That means the company
's profit has increased from Rs 693 crore to Rs 819
crore.  Which we see
growing at around 18%.
Talking about Earnings per share, it
stood at ₹16.49 in this quarter as against
₹15.6 in the last quarter and
₹14.5 in the last same quarter.  That means EPS has
increased from ₹14.5 to ₹16.49.
Which we see growing at around 17%.
So friends, on one
hand the company's sales seem to be increasing by about 12%.  At the
same time, we see the company's net profit
growing by around 18% and EPS
growing by around 17% on year-on-
year basis.  So,
how did you like ICICI LBD's quarter 2
results?  Please do let us know in the comments.
This video is only for education purpose.
If you like this video then don't forget to like,
share and subscribe
to Engineers Lab.  Here you get the
most detailed and engaging stock analysis.
So see you in the next video.  Till then,
happy investing, safe investing.
[music]